Next notice
Good morning
Nervous
Yoo-hoo!
It's the first take rehearsal!
It's the rehearsal for the demonstration practice!
I'm kind of nervous.
Because there are some irregularities
so we're going to rehearse the day before to make sure we're on the same page.
Rehearsal the day before
Good morning.
I think I'll buy a red coat too.
I can wear it because it's cold
I'm tying raw ah ah ah ah ah
bi
ah ah ah ah ah ah
e and tomoyo, we'll know one by one
It's okay, it's okay
Okay, now, let's get cute for the big class.
Connect them.
I'm super duper cute
Because you just broke up with me and you're the cutest thing I've ever seen.
That's the cutest.
And in the eyes.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Yes.
The cutest.
Like this one.
It's the cutest thing I've ever seen.
Bye-bye.
I don't have to do these two?
Yeah. - Okay.
Just this one?
Yeah.
I think it's cuter if we put them together.
The last one.
Yeah.
If you ask someone to put more pressure on it, you'll be in big trouble.
It could be really strong.
Not at all.
Gung kid.
For you.
All advanced.
Then, the Maiden Strikes Back!
The Maiden Strikes Back!
Are you scared?
You dumped me and I became superlatively pretty.
Thank you.
Come in, sister.
This way? It's this way.
Two of them sent me. They were so cute.
Soothing. Soothing.
Boo hoo! They're coming this way!
I'm not shaking, but I'll tell you.
I'm so cute right now.
I feel so cute.
All right.
Is it okay? I don't want to do the yuri color.
I want to do the lily color.
I'm looking forward to it.
I like headphones.
It's easier to sing with headphones.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ayameya Ayameya
And a lot of food here!
I usually take off my shoes
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
He looked so cool!
It's so cool!
Yes, sir.
Erebukku
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh!
Three... Oh, wow!
Three, I scooped it up!
Where are you sticky?
Oh, yeah.
You dumped me, Bundy.
Bundy.
Can I put this down for a second?
This master can tinker with one at a time. I don't think so.
I'll take this opportunity.
The master can tinker. Oh, that's fine.
Oh, I can tinker with it.
Ah~
Maybe they've already noticed.
I don't know, but I'll tell you.
It's cute.
I don't know why we're all doing this together.
Empty.
Isn't it a little different when it's empty?
Woof, woof, woof, woof.
I'm so cute right now.
Kiran.
This is huge!
I'm at my cutest right now.
I'm the cutest thing in the world right now because you rejected me.
Kiran.
This is the maiden's guest shooter.
I don't know if you've noticed by now, but...
I'll tell you.
I'm very pretty right now.
Oh, my God, you're gonna make me cry. You're so cute.
I don't care anymore, but...
You broke up with me, and it's the cutest thing ever.
The cutest crush I've ever had.
The cutest.
You just dumped me and I'm the cutest thing in the world.
I'm the most adorable crush in the history of my life
I'm the most adorable
Admit it... this is how a girl strikes back.
I'm the cutest of the cutest
I'm the cutest thing you've ever dumped me for
I don't know.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Are you doing this?
Are you doing it?
I'm not doing it.
We decided not to do this once.
I said before that we'd do it after the Tacky May Canner call and not at the end of the Hiyori song.
You said twice after the Hiyori song, right?
I'm not going to do it.
What about here? Here?
I'll do it here.
Where?
It says, "Tacky, I won't do it.
Oh, I did something.
It doesn't matter.
You don't have to do it.
I don't know.
But it doesn't have to be you, does it?
Yeah, I think so.
Let's do it as if it's the real thing.
Let's just pretend it's the real thing.
Okay, I'm getting nervous.
I'm gonna be nervous.
I'm going to be wild.
Disturbing.
Here, here.
Shoes.
Ear. Ear.
Ears.
Oh, maybe there's too much in there.
I'm sorry, I can't see this much.
Stop it with just one.
One is not so bad.
The big one.
Try two for now, and if it doesn't work, make it one.
You're Hynet. You're my lover.
I'm talking to you. What the hell is that?
No?
I'm the cutest!
I'm the cutest thing in the world.
I'm the cutest when I'm in the mood to be dumped.
That's how a girl strikes back.
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiyo
Thank you for watching!
You may have already noticed, but don't say it.
I'm so cute right now
You started this love and you're the one who ended it.
What's that, I'm gonna cry
That's so cute!
I can't believe you ditched me.
A friend of mine told me...
I told him that you've been in touch with me too much... because you're worried that I'm making you uncomfortable.
I don't care anymore.
But now that you dumped me...
I'm the cutest thing in the world.
The cutest crush I've ever had.
I'm the cutest thing in the world
That's a girl in a girl's play.
Yeah. - Okay.
Okay, we're done.
Wow, that's it.
You know what? I'd love to hear that. That's the soundtrack.
I want to hear it.
Yay, yay, yay!
Yes, I want to hear it.
Oh no.
It's tomorrow.
What in the world?
That's right.
The way you guys change is a little different than usual.
Really?
Changed?
It's not a video.
Yeah, it's not a video.
It's a little different, a little something.
I'm doing something that I don't usually do.
A special version.
I've practiced and I'm going to do my best for tomorrow.
I'll do my best.
Rest today, sleep a lot.
Let's sleep.
Let's sleep a lot.
Let's do our best.
I'm off.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I don't know why, but when I smile, it sure seems like the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure that somewhere, someone is crying, and I'm sure that somewhere, my body is wet again, and I'm sure that I'm not cold.
Someone somewhere must be crying, because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them.
I still don't know the scenery in front of me, look, let's go wherever you want to go
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, I paint a piece of the future, and it leads the way.
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiyo
If it's now...
me
Please subscribe to our channel!